alright guys welcome back to another video and if you ever want to make a program like Instagram or just want to
好吧欢迎 回到 另一个人 视频，如果你想做一个 喜欢Instagram的程序或只是想
make some cool photo filters and this is probably going to be one of the most important tutorials because I'm going to
制作一些很酷的照片滤镜，这是 可能会是一个 最 重要的教程，因为我要去
show you guys how to take pillow and use it to pretty much break up your image into separate channels
告诉你们如何采取枕头和使用 它几乎打破了你的形象 进入单独的 渠道
so again programs like Instagram and any like photo editing program uses all the
所以再次像Instagram 和任何程序 像照片编辑程序使用所有
time so let me go ahead and explain exactly what's going on for those of you who may not understand now whenever
时间让 我继续 解释 究竟是什么发生在你们身上 现在谁也不会理解
computers display images they don't display things like we just look at them
计算机显示他们没有的图像 显示我们只看他们的东西
in real life in real life you can like hold your hand two inches away from your face and you're not going to see any
在现实生活中， 你可以喜欢 握住你的手 离 你的 两英寸远 面对， 你不会 看到任何
pixels or anything like that however whenever your computer displays images
像素或类似的东西 但是 只要您的计算机显示图像
let me just zoom in right here you can see that every single image is actually
让我在这里放大 一下就可以了 看到每个图像都是 实际的
made up of these tiny things called pixels now it's pretty much a bunch of
由这些微小的东西组成 现在的像素这是一个很值得 一堆
individual boxes but when you zoom out it looks like a whole picture simple
单个盒子， 但缩小 时 看起来整个画面很简单
enough you guys probably already know what a pixel was now the thing I want to
你们可能 已经知道了 什么像素现在是我 想要 的东西
explain is this each one of those pixels pixels is actually made up of three
解释这 是 每个像素 像素实际上由三个组成
colors see right now this looks like I don't know like 100 different colors but
颜色现在看，这 看起来像我 不知道 100种不同颜色但是
each of these boxes are just a combination of three colors mixed
这些盒子中的每一个都 只是一个 混合三种颜色的组合
together with various amounts red green and blue now actually in Photoshop if
连同各种红绿色 而蓝色现在实际上是在Photoshop中
you click on channels you can see that that's all this image is this is the red
你点击你可以看到的频道 所有这些图像都是红色的
this is the green and this is the blue now you guys are like yeah right that's
这 是 绿色，这 是蓝色 现在你们就像是 的那样
just black and white for all of them I'm not yet well the black whenever we click
只有黑 和 白为所有这些我 我们点击时，黑色还不够好
on one of these channels it symbolizes how much red is in this channel how much
在这些 信道上 它象征 之一 这个频道多少红色多少钱
green is in this and how much blue now whenever we combine this much blue with
绿色就在这里，现在有多少蓝色 每当我们将这么多蓝色与之结合起来
this much green in this much red that's when we get this picture right here so again that's kind of key to remember
这个红色的绿色就是这么多绿色 当我们得到这样的画面就在这里 等等 再次，这是 记住 的关键
every single image is made up of three different colors
每个图像都由三个组成 不同的颜色
and it's pretty much saying this is how much of each color you add to get your whole image actually i'ma show you guys
它几乎就是这样说的 你添加 的 每种颜色都可以得到你的颜色 整个图像实际上 我告诉你们
this if you took this image and took out the red then of course you would only
这个如果你拿这个图像拿出来的话 那么红色当然你只会
have green and blue if you took out the green so I have like this purple because
如果拿出来的话，有绿色 和蓝色 绿色，所以我喜欢这个紫色，因为
it's only red and blue so on and so forth
它只有红色和蓝色等等 向前
all right so I guess that did take a little more than 60 seconds I lied but
好吧所以我想这确实需要一个 我哭了不到60秒，但是
now that we understand that let's go ahead and learn how to use pillow to
现在我们明白了， 让我们走吧 提前学习如何 使用枕头
take that image and break it up into these individual channels because right now just show you guys how to do it and
把那个图像分解成 这些个人渠道因为对 现在只是表明你们如何做到 这一点 ，
have this plan but later on I'm going to show you guys how you can take these
有这样的计划，但后来 我要去 告诉你们你们如何 能够接受这些
channels and tweak them to either edit the contrast or make some cool
频道并调整它们以进行编辑 对比或做一些酷
old-school effects stuff like that so the first thing we need is actually let
老派的效果类似的 东西 等等 我们需要的第一件事就是让它
me show you I probably should explain this now 99% of the images on your
我告诉你 我可能应该解释一下 这个现在99％的图像就在你身上了
computer or I'll say like 95 percent of them are going to be made up of three
电脑 或我会说95％的电脑 它们将由三个组成
channels red green and blue however sometimes people have images that are
然而，红色绿色和蓝色 有时人们是图片
CMYK and those are made up of four colors because those are better from
CMYK 和那些由 四个组成 颜色 因为那些 更好
like printing things in real life but in order to determine first that you
比如在现实生活中印刷东西但是在 为了先确定你
actually are working with image made up of three colors red green and blue what you can do is you can just print out the
实际上正在处理图像组成 三种颜色 红绿蓝什么的 你能做的就是你可以 打印出
mode of your image you can see whenever I run this it prints out the mode so
您可以随时查看 图像模式 我运行它打印出模式所以
this JPEG right here is RGB it means it is indeed made up of three and most of
这里的JPEG是RGB 意味着它 确实是由三个和大部分组成的
the time it is so you don't really have to worry about that but I felt like if I
你 没有真正 拥有的时间 担心这一点，但 我觉得 如果我
didn't tell you guys then you know people would complain so so now that we
没有告诉你们那么你 知道 现在人们会这么抱怨我们
verified that this image is indeed made up of three channels let's go ahead and
确认此图像 确实已制作完成 三个频道中的一个让我们继续前行
split them apart so the function is split them apart is of course call your
将它们分开以便功能如此 分开他们当然叫你的
image and call the function split now what this function does is it actually
图像并调用现在拆分的功能 这个功能实际上是做什么的
returns a tupple so it's going to return
返回一个 元组，所以它 会返回
three values and we're going to store those values in the variables r g b so
三个值，我们将要存储 那些变量rgb中的值 如此
again it's going to turn three values the first value we're
它会再次发生 把三个值变成我们的第一个值
going to store in the variable R the second one G and the third one be simple
要 存储在 变量 R中 第二个G和第三个很简单
enough so what these are are actually these channels so it's going to return
实际上这些是什么 这些渠道，所以它会回来
this for R this for G and this for B so if you don't believe me check this out
这对于 R此对于G和这对于B 所以 如果你不相信我，请检查 一下
if you go down and you just hit our show and run this I'm just going to show you
如果你 走 ，你 只需点击 我们的节目 并运行这个我只是要告诉你
that red channel and you can actually do this for green and blue too so now I'm
那个红色通道，你可以真正做到 这对于绿色 和蓝色也是如此，现在我
going to show my green one and now I'm going to show my blue one and actually I
要显示我的绿色，现在我 要显示我的 蓝色 ，实际上是我
kind of like doing this like to close out all of these and run these all at
有点喜欢这样做 关闭 从所有这些和运行 这些都在
the same time because it just looks cool in Photoshop our G B I don't know I
同时 因为它看起来很酷 在Photoshop我们的G B 我不知道我
think that's so cool it's actually probably kind of stupid but I think it's
认为这 实在 太 酷了 可能有点愚蠢，但我认为是
kind of cool so again now we have pretty much three separate images created or
有点酷， 所以现在我们很漂亮 创建了三个单独的图像或
three image objects one is the red Channel ones the green Channel and ones
三个图像对象一个是红色 通道那些绿色 通道和 个
the blue Channel so now we can do cool things like arm
蓝色频道 所以现在我们可以做一些像手臂这样的酷事
well actually I'll show you guys something really cool in the next story
实际上，我会告诉 你们 在下一个故事中真的很酷
because I'm kind of running out of time don't want my file to get too big so well the next tutorial is going to be
因为我有点没时间了 不希望我的文件 变得太大 以及接下来的教程将 是
awesome I'll see you then
真棒 那一会儿见